Designed an arcade co-op rougelike with a top-down view, with emphasis on collaboration and theorycrafting.
Brought the game's vision to life with all departments and held weekly meet ups to keep everyone up to date.
Led a technical team of 14 programmers, designers, animators, and shader artists to our first published game.
Developed a deterministic procedural animation system to simplify development.
Won Rookie awards 2024 "Game of the year - People's choice".
Designed a stealth-action hybrid with character transformations and multiuse skills.
Authored diegetic UI using VFXs to immerse the player.
Programmed skills, camera, and movement, that changed based on character transformation.
Programmed AI that reacts intuitively to weather conditions and visibility issues.
Developed tools to easily place AI agents and control patrol paths.
Designed a minimalistic meditative sci-fi puzzle game.
Managed scope creep to deliver the project in time.
Programmed systemic physics changes and story events.
Wrote multi-layered lore and screenplay for the game.
Developed a realistic black hole shader.
Designed an addictive game loop for mobile with only two controls.
Developed an easy to work on level design pipeline.
Achieved low-end mobile device compatibility.
Successfully managed scope creep to deliver the project in time.
Programmed a dynamic difficulty system that significantly increase repeatability.