Programmed camera to continuously follow characters in cutscenes and awkward map locations.
Programmed responsive and fun character skills.
Programmed multiple procedural systems and a custom attribute system that favored ease of development.
Designed an arcade co-op rougelike with a top-down view, with emphasis on collaboration and theorycrafting.
Won Rookie awards 2024 "Game of the year - People's choice".
Programmed level design tools that helped to control enemies and story events.
Programmed skills, camera, and movement, that changed based on character transformation.
Programmed AI that reacts intuitively to weather conditions and visibility issues.
Developed tools to easily place AI agents and control patrol paths.
Designed a stealth-action hybrid with character transformations and multiuse skills.
Programmed systemic physics changes and story events.
Designed a minimalistic meditative sci-fi puzzle game.
Managed scope creep to deliver the project in time.
Wrote multi-layered lore and screenplay for the game.
Developed a realistic black hole shader.
Programmed a dynamic difficulty system that significantly increase repeatability.
Added an infinite procedural map that followed dynamic difficulty.
Designed an addictive game loop for mobile with only two controls.
Successfully managed scope creep to deliver the project in time.
Mixed, mastered, and programmed sound and music for the game.